[
  {
    "Front": "χαίρω",
    "Back": " vb.: er glad"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χαλεπός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: vanskelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χαλκός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: bronze"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χάρις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: glæde, taknemmelighed"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χειµών",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: vinter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χείρ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: hånd"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χείρων",
    "Back": " adj. 3: ringere"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χίλιοι",
    "Back": " num. adj. 1-2: tusind"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χορός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: dansegruppe"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χράοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: bruger"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χρή",
    "Back": " vb.: det er nødvendigt"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χρήµατα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n. (plur.): penge"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χρόνος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: tid"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χρυσός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: guld"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χῶρα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: jord(stykke)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "χωρίς",
    "Back": " præp. m. gen.: uden"
  }
]